## RESUME

Deepika C B C/o Sri Lakshmi sreenivasa ladies PG Narayan reddy layout Hosur main road Electronic city phase 2 Bangalore-560100

> Email id: deepikagowda116@gmail.com. Mobile No: 9844170437

#### Career Objective:

Intend to build a career in a leading corporate hi-tech environment with committed and dedicated people, which will help me to explore myself fully and realize my potential. As a motivated and dedicated professional, I am willing to work as a key player in a challenging and creative environment.

#### **Professional Summary**

Experienced Data Analytics', skilled at interpreting, evaluating, and creating solutions for various business-oriented sophisticated systems & processes enabling profitable business operations with customer-centric solutions. Excellent managerial and interpersonal faculties are invaluable to ensuring tasks and projects are conducted in a timely and successful manner at all times.

#### **Experience Summary:**

HUSTLER EQUIPMENT INTERNATIONAL LIMITED.

Senior Executive -2022 Till Date

Handling Team Meetings.
Daily, Weekly, Monthly, and Quarterly Reports.
Maintaining PO's Control Sheet.
Preparing Presentations for Team meetings.
Handling Logistics and Container dispatch documents follow-up with suppliers.
Container documents are uploaded on Smartsheet.

Photos & Dispatch documentation files storage of each order PO wise (Stage inspection	
Dispatch)	
Handling Backend report.	
Payments and PO's Status follow-up with Suppliers.	
Maintaining Bookkeeping, filing, Schedule meetings, and Schedule for travel plan	
arrangements and accommodations.	
Coordinate with the Global supply chain team.	
Handling HR Executive Works like salaries, incentives, holidays Etc.	
Inventory list Audit & Asset list Audit.	
Planning for production Forecasting.	
Maintaining Vendor List.	
Quotations follow up with Suppliers.	
Various kinds of reports.	
Checking drawings and interacting with suppliers etc.	
Supply Chain Executive – Nov'22 till date	
Forecasting requirement /Qtr Targets	
SCM- Generate Pos& Drawings issued with Vendors, Update PO List, Daily worm report,	
Daily & Weekly Production status followups, Update PPTs, Container Sheet updated,	
Payment status followups Etc.	
Container Plan, Container Loading Monitor, Container Tracking details, Logistics payments	
followups, Container damages, Container loading snaps uploaded, Container documents	
collected, and Airfreight & courier followups.	
Air Fright and Sea fright containers tracking and followups.	
POs , Vendors payments followups.	
POs creation, Inventry management, vendors status follows Raw material sourcing,taking	
care of supplu sourcing, Coordination with internal teams by understanding their	
requirements.	
Ensuring the adequate supply of all required materials, components and equipment.	
Manage purchasing shortage list and ensure material is ordered and expedited in a timely manner and communicate to production.	
Releasing POs to the shortlisted suppliers and ensuring materials and docked to the company	
based on the need date.	

#### AUDI BENGALURU-JUBLIANT MOTORS WORKS PVT LTD.

Designation: MIS Executive.

Duration: Feb 1<sup>st,</sup> 2016 to 2019. Expert in Multiple reports working with formula, Pivot Chart, Pivot Table, and various other excel sheet components for accurate data. Summary Reports, quality Pledge & E-mails sent to customers, 

Prepare Monthly Technician Productivity & Incentive Report. ☐ Maintained Driver's Time Tracker Report & Incentive report. ☐ Update Team data tracker & MIS Dashboard on Daily, Weekly & Monthly Reports Etc. Data collection and prepare dealer reports for Bangalore, Mangalore, Pune, and Chennai). Advanced presentation in MS PowerPoint to Present MIS & Other related important reports. ☐ Coordinate and communicate with multiple teams in Business Technology.  $\Box$  Analyze errors in software applications and coordinate with vendors & resolve the issues. Promotion to Corporate Office –MIS EXECUTIVE (Jubilant Motors Works Pvt Ltd). Handling 7 Markets & MG Dealers – 4 locations – (2019 -2022) (6 Years) Group Team data tracker & MIS Dashboard on Daily, Weekly & Monthly & Yearly Reports Etc. ☐ Handling locations-wise new software portals. Analyze errors in software applications and coordinate with vendors & resolve the issues and upload daily data. Coordinate and communicate with multiple teams' Service Heads. Preparing Performance PPT Process & Business-wise Generate Daily/Monthly/Yearly by using advanced excel functions Handle Team queries about their Incentive, Target & Achievement. Arranging the data according to the format. Prepare data as per process requirement. Handling alone 7 branches data and documents. Consolidated downtime report and track the record daily. Maintain Technician's Incentive Reports based on productivity. Quality Reports. Worked on ad-hoc requests as per requirements. Tracked different metrics daily and organized them for ease of use. Updating Data Tracker and MIS Dashboard on a daily and weekly basis. 

Handling multiple reports, working with MS-Excel, different formulas and various others excel sheet components for accurate data. ☐ Create Various MIS Reports.						
BMW-NAVNIT MOTORS PVT LTD.						
Designation: CRE After Sales - Exposure as Service Assistant &Data Analytics. Duration: July 12 <sup>th,</sup>						
2012, to Jan 31 <sup>st</sup> , 2016 (3.5 years)						
Job Description.						
☐ Supporting High profile clientele as per BMW Standards						
Follow-up of payments from Insurance						
☐ Analyzing Workshop productivity and preparing Technician & drivers incentive						
☐ Following up on the Payment outstanding report,						
☐ Daily, Weekly & Monthly reports,						
☐ Service job card opened, System Work						
☐ Monthly & Yearly Prepare Presentation. (P.P.T.)						
☐ Coordinate with Service Engineer's & Technician's Teams.						
Certification of Appreciation:						
☐ Best Employee in 2017/18 from Jubilant Motor Works.						
$\square$ Best Performer Employee – 2020 (Corporate Office).						
☐ Best Most Supporting Performer in 2021 from Jubilant Motor Works. (Corporate Office).						

# **Educational Profile:**

Completed M.COM in 2012 from ManasaGangothri in Mysore, with 53%.
Completed BBM in 2010 from Government First Grade College, Pandavapura, Karnataka
with 62%.
Completed Intermediate (P.U.C) in 2007Girls PU College, Pandavapura, Karnataka, with
75.8 %.

Completed 5.5.L.C in 2005 from Board of Secondary Education, Ramataka with 597		Completed S.S.L.C in	2005 from Board of Secondary	y Education, Karnataka with 59%.
--	--	----------------------	------------------------------	----------------------------------

# Personal Details:

Name	Deepika C B
Father's Name	Balaraju C E
Marital Status	Single
Date Of Birth	12.06.1989
Nationality	Indian
Religion	Hindu
Languages Known	Kannada, English, Hindi.
Hobbies	Listening to Music, Watching TV, Cooking Etc

Computer Skills	Internet Explore & Tally 0.9 & PowerPoint, MS Excel, MS Word, VLOOKUP, Pivot Table & Chart & Concatenate, Count If, Average, Drop down list formula, Vlookup& Advance Excel
Present Address	C/o Sri Lakshmi sreenivasa ladies PG Narayan reddy layout Hosur main road Electronic city phase 2 Bangalore-560100
Permanent Address	D/o Balaraju C E Chikkade, Pattasomanahalli Post, Pandavapura Taluk-571434 Mandya District, Karnataka

### Declaration:

I hereby declare that the above information is true to the best of my knowledge and belief, and I shall be held responsible for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars

Date :

Place : Bangalore (Deepika C B)